A Royal Christmas Crush is a tv movie, comedy,
romance film directed by Marita Grabiak.
Ava accepts the opportunity of a lifetime to work at the Royal Ice Hotel which leads her to a
surprise whirlwind romance with the most important guest of all, the Royal Prince himself.
Prince Henry, played by Stephen Huszar.
Ava Jensen, played by Katie Cassidy.
Uncle Karl, played by Charlie Ebbs.
Brigitta, played by Angela Besharah.
Deputy Von Trier, played by Glenn Edward Gyorffy.
Sigrid, played by Kathryn Kohut.
Many Christmas stories have been adapted to feature films and TV specials,
and have been broadcast and repeated many times on television.
Since the popularization of home video in the 1980s, these films are sold
and re-sold every year during the holiday shopping season.
Many television networks, film studios, and production companies, such as cable television channels Hallmark and Lifetime, produce and
release new Christmas-themed films every year during or around December, all with variations of similar plots and themes.
Additionally, films revolving around the Nativity story of Christmas are regularly
produced such as The Nativity Story (2006) and The Star (2017).
One film that has become the flashpoint for "Is this a Christmas movie or not?" debates is Die Hard (1988), with some viewing the film as a
Christmas movie intertwined with an action genre setting or a film that is simply set around the Christmas and holiday season.
The film explores themes of sequel, christmas, christmas romance.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.